

I'm passionate about technology, science, developing things that improve people's lives and make the world a better place. I've been working with mobile development for iOS platform since 2014 with experience on all steps of iOS development, from the concept of the ideas until releasing the app on the store and following the results with analytics, tests and crashreports.

## **EXPERIENCE**

TVOS | IOS DEVELOPER ▼ FREECAST INC Since January 2021, Working with Swift for iOS and tvOS apps

IOS ENGINEER  $\nabla$  PAGSEGURO UOL

July 2018 - March 2021, Working with native apps using Swift

IOS DEVELOPER **▼ STORMBREAKER STUDIOS** 

January 2020 - December 2020, Working in iOS apps using Swift

IOS DEVELOPER **▽ BRQ** 

April 2017 - June 2018, Working with native apps using Swift and Objective-C

IOS DEVELOPER **▼ MAGNA SISTEMAS** 

February 2016 - April 2017, Working with native apps using Swift

IOS DEVELOPER ▼ URBAN SUMMER

March 2015 - February 2016, Working with native and hybrid apps

## **EDUCATION**

SYSTEM ANALYSIS AND DEVELOPMENT

Learning algorithms, software engineer, databases, software development in FMU, Sao Paulo, Brazil

IOS DEVELOPER

Learning a lot of concepts about iOS development in Impacta, Sao Paulo, Brazil

## **SKILLS**

- Xcode
- SwiftUI
- > git
- MVC >
- >
- cocoapods

Auto Layout

- Swift
- Obj-C
- **MVVM**
- >
- SPM >
- Agile Methodologies